<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BETTer</string>
    <string name="title_activity_better">better</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="menu_tools">Tools</string>
    <string name="menu_share">Share</string>
    <string name="menu_send">Send</string>
    <string name="confidential_information">Confidential Information</string>
    <string name="terms_service">Terms of Service</string>
    <string name="privacy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="agree">AGREEMENT TO TERMS</string>
    <string name="agree_terms"><u>Agree To Terms</u></string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Last updated 28th, February 2020</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy1">INTRODUCTION</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy2">BETTer (“we” or “us” or “our”) respects the privacy of our users (“user” or “you”). This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, and safeguard your information when you visit our website BETTer.com, BETTer app, including any other media form, media channel, mobile website, or mobile application related or connected thereto (collectively, the “Site”). Please read this privacy policy carefully. If you do not agree with the terms of this privacy policy, please do not access the site. We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. We will alert you about any changes by updating the “Last Updated” date of this Privacy Policy. Any changes or modifications will be effective immediately upon posting the updated Privacy Policy on the Site, and you waive the right to receive specific notice of each such change or modification.
You are encouraged to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed of updates. You will be deemed to have been made aware of, will be subject to, and will be deemed to have accepted the changes in any revised Privacy Policy by your continued use of the Site after the date such revised Privacy Policy is posted.</string>
    <string name="terms"> We as the developers of this app need to collect data about students in order for this app to function. Where this information comprises personal data, us as the developers must comply with the principles set out in the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and the provisions contained in the Data Protection Act 2018.
    Personal Data
    Your data can only be processed in the following circumstances:
    1.	with the consent of the individual;
    2.	compliance with a legal obligation;
    3.	for the performance of a task carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in the controller; or
    4.	for the legitimate interests of the data controller or a third party, unless prejudicial to the interests of the individual.
    Agreement
    1.	These Terms and Conditions apply to the developers of the app and the person using the Service.
    2.	We will not share your data with third parties.
    3.	We will not use your data for longer than necessary.
    4.	Your data shall be processed lawfully, fairly and in a transparent manner.
    5.	Your data shall be collected for specified, explicit and legitimate lawful purposes and shall not be further processed in any manner incompatible with those purposes;
    6.	Your data shall be adequate, relevant, and limited to what is necessary in relation to the purposes for which they are processed;
    7.	Your data shall be kept in a form which permits identification of individuals for no longer than is necessary for the purposes for which the personal data are processed;
    8.	Your data shall be processed in a manner that ensures appropriate security of the personal data.
    9.	Subject to your acceptance of this agreement you are of your own will sharing your data and will be able to use this app.
</string>
</resources>
